What's up? Good to see you.
>> Great to see you.
>> Thank you guys for uh traveling. I know
it's not I know it's a long way from DC,
although uh a little hot, but it's
pretty nice out there. And uh anyway,
>> worst places to be.
>> No, worst places to be. What what what
can I What can I help with?
>> Um
what's what's the latest on the stadium?
Is it on track for your time?
>> On track. On track. Totally on track. Uh
hard at work on
so many cool things when you start to
think about it. But basically, uh we're
starting utility construction this
month. Uh next year, about this time,
we'll start construction. We're picking
uh we're doing some of the detailed
design features. And you know, there's
so many cool opportunities with the
innovation in stadiums. I mean, I, you
know, whether it's the shape of the
scoreboard, which we may have some
things up our sleeve on, whether it's um
size of the scoreboard, the sound, uh
this the nature of the roof, uh you
know, where the premium, how close many
of the seats are relative to other
stadiums. There's so many great
opportunities, but we're definitely on
track and looking forward. This is going
to be an amazing project. It's the
funnest part of every week for me is
spending several hours on the stadium.
>> And then you guys are um introducing
some new uniforms in April.
>> I you know giving away state secrets. So
what kind of went into the process and
how much of a priority was that for you
when you came in?
>> Yeah, it's the priority is uh honoring
our past and then looking to the future,
right? updating um but but not
forgetting about um our heritage, who we
are, and honoring that. And so we have a
bunch of things up our sleeve. I don't
want to ruin the surprise, but uh uh
we're going to continue to, you know, go
back and try to embrace our past, but
then update it. Uh and so stay tuned.
>> Why was that important to you to to
undergo that part of it? Why to embrace
all that? Why was that important? Well,
because I lived I mean I lived through
our p I mean some of I didn't I'm only
61 so I I didn't I didn't go back before
the 70s but I was there for the 70s 80s
and early 90s right and so I lived
through how amazing those teams were and
you know what an impact it had on me and
I know that thousands of our fans or
millions maybe feel the same way and so
um I think it's important to go back to
that as much as you can But you at the
same time uh we have a bright future
ahead. So um if you even the shape of
the stadium and the look of the stadium
right when you look at it um it looks
like RFK it doesn't but it's been
modernized right and so that's a great
example and so our uniforms are similar.
I mean, some of the Super Bowl area
uniforms, uh, some, you know, going, you
know, there's a many ways to honor, uh,
our past and you're seeing how we treat,
uh, athletes, uh, and, you know, bring
back some of our past superstars. So,
all those things go into it.
>> So, and also for you guys coming off the
season, you had a lot of aggressive
moves, coordinators, and all that. What
have you thought about the approach to
the off season, and it just feels like
there's a heightened sense of urgency as
Dan kind of?
>> Uh, there is. Uh, look, no, no one was
happy with last season. Um,
and um we um we we wanted to make a lot
of progress and so we um you know,
obviously made some changes and then I
think Adam and Dan had a great free
agency. Uh we, you know, picked up a lot
of great players. I think as you all
know, uh we now next up is the draft.
And so pretty much every waking hour
we're trying to improve our team and uh
we want to go back. You know, we had an
amazing first year, a tougher second
year, but we have a lot of you, we have
a young quarterback that we have a lot
of faith in and you know, time's a
wasting and we got to get on it and
that's what we're doing.
>> Josh, nowadays in the NFL, you see a lot
of
quick trigger moves when it comes to
coaches.
Going into year three, coming off the
year, you guys just had reaffirmed your
Yeah, both Dan and Adam have our u have
have my confidence have our confidence.
uh we're behind them and um we made the
changes we thought were appropriate uh
under their leadership and um and one of
the great things was that uh the minute
uh you know like I said no one was happy
with last season but we immediately got
on it right and they got on it and you
know sometimes there were some injuries
there were some other things that
happened but none of that's an excuse
and so we knew we had a lot of work to
do and that's what and and and watching
them you know get back at it quickly Um
Dan ran an incredible process for the
coordinators. Uh met with tons of
people. I was very much up to date and
you know obviously
uh we ended up with uh two guys that I
think are you know a little younger but
um really uh have massively high
ceilings uh and I think can hopefully
have a big impact on our franchise. And
so, um, you know, and then Adam took
over, you know, got, you know, right
into free agency and you saw the
activity. Uh, obviously,
uh, you know, the, uh, it took a little
time for us to get started, but, that's
sometimes the way things are, right? and
he uh made uh a lot of important moves
to get the team younger
um and to get the team faster and to go
back to uh hopefully players that can
deliver a more aggressive playing style
and uh you know obviously you know our
you know our front seven our pass rush
is going to be much improved way deeper
there uh picked up some offensive
weapons
um and um and so looking for resigned uh
LT, you know, Marcus. Um, and so, you
know, we made a lot of progress, right?
But the good news is we now have the
draft and, uh, we have a very high draft
pick. Uh, and we're going to get a great
player there.
>> Josh, considering the importance of
Jaden, what did you think of the way?
>> Yeah, look, I think that um, Jaden um,
you know, we have a lot of confidence in
Jaden. I spoke with him yesterday. I
keep in touch with him. He's working
super hard in the offseason. I got to
say I was a, you know, when he lined up
uh in flag football, I'm not going to
say I wasn't nervous, but uh you know,
glad that we got through that one. And
um you know, he's you know, our guy. You
know, we have a lot of faith in him and
um and so he's hard at work learning uh
and and implementing you know, what's
going to change with uh you know, David
Blau. And so, um, you know, listen,
moving forward and excited about next
season and, you know, sometimes injuries
happen and other things happen and, uh,
good news about Jaden is that he's right
back at work. And, um, and I I have a
lot of confidence in him.
>> With the flag football stuff, is that
like a league priority?
Ask you if your star players can be
participating.
>> Yeah. So, that's it is a league priority
in the sense that like flag creates uh,
you know, inclusivity in football,
right? It's very hard. I mean, you know,
you need to be It's harder to play
tackle football for girls, for women,
for people that might not be big enough
or fast enough. And what it does is it
expands the sport greatly. I mean,
obviously in something like that, right,
that was really Jaden's call. Um, the
league doesn't really get involved in
that. And everyone took their own point
of view on that. And my point of view
was that that Jaden's uh someone I
trust. He's an individual. He's a he's a
grown man. He's a grown person and you
know I left that decision up to him.
>> I wanted to follow up too because you
had the famous line.
New report cards are out. You guys have
placed so high all them. How important
is that to you?
>> Incredibly important. So uh it's good to
not it's good to have an a uh more work
to do. Look, I think for us, um, we went
to the players. Our process was to go
talk to the players directly, right? To
have Adam talk to the players, to have
Dan talk to players, to have myself talk
to the players, and say, look, what can
we do different? What can we do better?
And there's a very, look, players win
titles, players win Super Bowls. Um and
and so getting that having um the patina
and also the respect of the players um
that we care about what they think and
we make we actually act on it. That's
really important. So I was it's good to
see that but uh our process was to go
direct and we continue to do that.
>> What is the um plan for the health group
um with Tim going back to Australia?
>> Yeah. So, I mean, obviously, there's
nothing more important than the health
and the safety of our players. And so,
it's a massively strategic area for us.
And so, what we're doing is um we're
right now meeting a lot of people and
Adam's leading a search to hire a new
head of player care. And clearly, um as
an NFL team, you know, you're looking
for every way to advantage yourself. and
one obviously being like a home for
amazing players where they feel like
you're taking care of them that's a
massive advantage and then and so like
we're working really hard it's a really
strategic priority for the team for the
club and you know you can you know I
know you're going to speak to Adam later
and he's um he's he's front and center
on that
>> stadium
but
the naming of the
Yeah. So, we're we're about four years
or more away from that. So, we're that's
not right now. We're focused on building
a great stadium. Uh having an amazing
fan experience. I mean, one of the
things I'll say about the stadium is
that uh you know, it's not just uh a
stadium. It's going to be you know,
that's a small part of what's going to
be four neighborhoods. And uh it's going
to be really uh a community for the DMV.
And so like the first step is building
the stadium and you know we're targeting
uh 75,000
you know kind of seats or availability.
Uh we want to host amazing events. We're
trying to get the women's world cup uh
to play there. Uh and you know all the
best acts will play there. And so, um,
there's so many things to do, but, uh,
the naming rights is kind of way off.
>> Good try.
>> Four years, huh?
>> Yeah. So, we're investing, so we're
we're investing about 25 million this
year across the uh, practice uh,
facility and the uh, stadium. Most of
that's going to stadium. Uh we've
invested over 100 million in stadium and
we're still upgrading that. I mean
obviously we didn't inherit a great
situation there. But look ultimately
right you have to keep your fans happy.
You have to keep the city happy and the
DMV happy and you know you got to you
got to just lean in unfortunately. So
those are going to be some lower ROI
investments but we want to you know make
sure that everyone has a first class
experience and do what we can do there.
Is there any
space or is this going to modernize?
We're literally just what we're doing is
we're modernizing all the meeting rooms,
the fitness center. Uh you obviously saw
we took took that incredible
high school feel that reminded me of my
high school but 30 years later. Um and
you know this year um we're you know
changing the showers just a lot like the
the player facil facilities themselves
where they hang out and just making it a
really comfortable place. It's not
really about expanding footprint and you
know right now we're you know listen
like we have a lot on our plate and so
it's not like I mean right now there's
no real plans to leave. People love that
area. Um the team loves it. Uh that
doesn't mean
that will never leave. But right now,
we're focused on the stadium and so like
making that a great place is important
to us.
>> About a year ahead of curious front
office
contract kind of what that back and
forth process is.
>> Yeah. So right now um I've had the
opportunity now to go through um my
second free agency with Adam and um this
year they made a lot of progress on
systems on analytics on there's just an
incredible amount of information that
they develop around these player
signings particularly the bigger ones
and they have a whole library of
information uh everything from medical
to interviews to what they've heard
through analytics to scouting thing and
so it's all available and so uh that
gives me a lot of confidence uh to
support what they want to do and so it
gives me a lot of confidence to lean
into these big signings but in a big
signing like that I mean obviously I'm
consulted but generally I'm going to
defer you know to to Adam and and what
he wants to do and so far you know and
and like I said for me the confidence my
confidence is growing in the sense that
when someone gives me a lot of
information and they have an incredible
rationale developed and then like
obviously you do comps. I mean we're in
a hard cap system, right? So you you try
to figure out okay you know what's the
right level of compensation as well.
>> What have you learned from owning other
teams that you know going through all
this in the past that maybe you've been
able to apply here last couple years
where they're dealing with a season like
that or dealing with free agency
decisions and that kind of stuff.
>> Yeah, I mean I've learned a lot. I mean
obviously the the longer you're around
many things are the same in terms of uh
it's all about people right so uh Adam
his staff like the technology that they
bring in the medical that they bring in
the process they follow um that
ultimately and and your level of
confidence in those people allows you to
lean in uh and so number one you know
it's about picking the right people
developing the organization
um and developing you know these various
systems and you improve them every year.
So that's the first thing and secondly
it's about and by people also it's about
players right and you know it's not and
you know it's like talent but also who
they are as people where how they are in
the locker room how much they love the
game of football. uh so all those softer
things you know come into it as well and
so that that those are some of the
learnings that I've gotten and clearly I
mean I've seen you know systems across
different sports and so I' I have much
more of a frame of reference now as to
what what's really good and what's not
so good and so again you know we had a
big free agency and you know what I
learned right is that it's like boom
boom boom boom boom I mean you know at
some level um you know you have to let
go and trust the people that are working
with you. Uh you're not going to be able
to like, you know, keep up. You're going
to have to defer to them because the
thing is so fast moving and so you do a
lot of upfront prep work. You talk a
lot, but then things change, right? And
you know, the market for free agency
changes, right, every day. And so you're
deferring. So who's in that seat? And in
this case, it's Adam, you know, is so
important to what's going on.
>> To that point, aren't major free as a
player there are some of those questions
where there's a fractured relationship
there's questions about the commitment
to the game how do you get involved
there
>> it's really the same way like I I'm
obviously a presence in the room
um I'm listening I'm asking questions um
you know making sure that um there's
some rationality to it and what I find
is that you know Adam has a very
disciplined and rational approach. He
know he's he thinks about it up front.
He understands where he wants to go. Uh
him and his staff. He has he has a good
staff and and so um it's sort of the
same thing where I'm deferring but I
mean to a large extent but then you know
like obviously if you're if you're
basically overruling your GM you know
that's not going to last very long.
That's not the way the league works
>> with the the NFL draft a year in
advance. Um I know a lot of planning
over the next year. How how much is the
team involved in that and how much are
you sort of looking at what Pittsburgh
is doing this year?
>> Yeah. So we're going to go visit
Pittsburgh. That's just all getting
started. I mean obviously
you know it hasn't even happened yet,
right? But right after that, it's but
it's really the business team. And
listen, that's a massively important
thing for us and for the DMV and for the
NFL and for the nation, right? So,
that'll be uh we we'll there'll be high
stress on our side. We're going to be
working really hard to be amazing hosts.
me putting on, you know, I visited San
Francisco and watched the Super Bowl
this year and how great of a job they
did. And uh, you know, we needed to do
that. You know, the draft is a huge
thing, right? There we we estimate
there'll be over a million people on the
National Mall. I mean, that's a big deal
that there there hasn't been that crowd
in a long in years and years, maybe
forever, right? Uh so I think that uh
you know all eyes will be upon us and we
need to be amazing hosts make sure
everything goes well work with the city
um and really exciting really exciting
time for us.
>> You saw what a saw a mess the Max C
situation became in Baltimore with that.
Is there anything that the league can do
to maybe head off or prevent a situation
like that from happening?
>> Yeah, I'm going to defer that question
to the league as you might imagine. Uh,
we saw it. I mean, obviously, it was
unusual.
>> Question.
>> It was unusual.
Uh, I'll leave it at that.
>> Okay.
>> Time for two more.
>> You're looking at the changes in the
uniforms. Has there been any discussion
about the WO?
>> Yeah, we're always looking at this
stuff. And like I said, um, you know,
we're committed to the commander's name.
Um, I'm going to leave. We have a lot of
surprise up our sleeve this this season.
I think people will be I'm excited to
see the reaction. I think we've got it
right and I'm gonna leave it to you know
the surprise situation to allow everyone
to enjoy it.
>> It was a masterful way of
>> well done.
>> Yeah,
you talked about bring them back. Um
have you got any feedback from them?
What's it like and looking back last
year? Do you have favorite moments or
things you want to see? Yeah, look, I
mean, obviously for me personally, it
it's a really important those were
warriors that are part of our heritage
and part of who we are. And so, you
know, obviously the, you know, being
there with Daryl Green, being there with
Art Monk, showing up at Art Monk's house
and watching the surprise on his face
was, you know, a moment I'll remember
the rest of my life. But, um, you know,
obviously there've been a lot there's
been a lot more than that. And so, we
have more up our sleeve there, too.
There's there's an obvious one we need
to take care of and we're working on
that. Um and but but you know there's so
many uh people to honor that we're going
to keep doing it.
>> All right. Thanks, John.
>> Thank you. Byebye. Appreciate it.
Nice to see you